[{"question": "  okay!  listen, i&#146;m gonna be moving out so you will be in charge of paying the rent.", "answer": " right! and when is that due?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 1, "asentId": 2}, {"question": " first of the month.", "answer": " and that&#146;s every month?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 3, "asentId": 4}, {"question": " no, just the months you actually want to live here.", "answer": " ahhh.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 5, "asentId": 6}, {"question": "  oh my god!!", "answer": " that&#146;s our phone number. now look, i know i kinda sprung this whole me moving out on thing, so why don&#146;t i just&#151;why don&#146;t i just cover you for a while?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 9, "asentId": 10}, {"question": " no-no! no way! joey tribbiani does not take charity&#133;anymore.", "answer": " it&#146;s not charity, joe&#133;", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 11, "asentId": 12}, {"question": " no! forget it! okay&#151;i mean thanks, but i&#146;m done taking money from you. all right, i can take of myself. now, what&#146;s next? come on.", "answer": " okay uh, here&#146;s the electric bill.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 13, "asentId": 14}, {"question": " this is how much we pay for electric?!!!", "answer": " uh, yeah.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 15, "asentId": 16}, {"question": " so is joey going to have to give up the apartment?", "answer": " no, i hope not! i tried to offer him some money, but he wouldn&#146;t take it.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 19, "asentId": 20}, {"question": " well, how much do you think he needs?", "answer": " i figure that $1,500 would cover him for a few months, y&#146;know? but i have to trick him into taking it so i won&#146;t hurt his pride.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 21, "asentId": 22}, {"question": " why don&#146;t you hire him as an actor? you could have him dress up and put on little skits. whatever you want.", "answer": " well that would help the pride thing.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 23, "asentId": 24}, {"question": "  hey!", "answer": " hey! wow! you look great! wanna move in with me tomorrow?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 25, "asentId": 26}, {"question": "  okay.", "answer": " okay!  so, what do you girls have planned for tonight?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 27, "asentId": 28}, {"question": " well, instead of being sad that tonight is my last night together with rachel we thought we&#146;d go out to dinner and celebrate the fact that rachel is moving in with phoebe.", "answer": " and also, my birthday.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 29, "asentId": 30}, {"question": " it&#146;s not your birthday.", "answer": " what a mean thing to say! i would never tell you it&#146;s not your birthday!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 31, "asentId": 32}, {"question": " hey!", "answer": " hey!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 33, "asentId": 34}, {"question": " hey!", "answer": " hey! so you guys have anything planned for the big last night?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 35, "asentId": 36}, {"question": " well, instead of just hanging out, we figure we&#146;d do nothing.", "answer": " whoa-whoa-whoa, knicks season opener tonight. i thought maybe you guys would come over and watch it.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 37, "asentId": 38}, {"question": " i don&#146;t know ross, not if you&#146;re gonna talk about how you gave up a career in basketball to become a paleontologist.", "answer": " i did give up a career in basketball to become a paleontologist!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 39, "asentId": 40}, {"question": "  pheebs, i was wondering&#133;", "answer": " you&#146;re not dressed yet?! we&#146;re supposed to start having fun in 15 minutes!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 41, "asentId": 42}, {"question": " well and clearly not a minute sooner.", "answer": " rachel, you are packed though right, i mean please tell me that you&#146;re packed.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 43, "asentId": 44}, {"question": " of course i packed! monica relax! i just wanted to ask phoebe her opinion on what i should wear tonight.", "answer": " my god, i can&#146;t get a minute of peace around this place.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 45, "asentId": 46}, {"question": " oh my god! monica&#146;s just gonna kill you.", "answer": " yeah, yeah, i know.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 47, "asentId": 48}, {"question": " well, what you&#146;re wearing is fine for that.", "answer": "  rachel, i need to borrow&#151;you&#146;re not packed!!!! you&#146;re not packed even a little bit!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 49, "asentId": 50}, {"question": " surprise!!", "answer": " what?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 51, "asentId": 52}, {"question": " no, no don&#146;t get mad because look&#151;this is what happened. so i-i started packing, then i realized, &quot;what am i doing? i am lousy at packing!&quot; right? but you love packing! so, as a gift to you, on our last night, ta-da!", "answer": "  i&#146;ll be coordinator! oh my god! i&#146;m so sorry, i didn&#146;t get you anything! okay, look everybody has to help! okay? you can help, can&#146;t you phoebe?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 53, "asentId": 54}, {"question": " i have plans.", "answer": " you&#146;re plans were with us.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 55, "asentId": 56}, {"question": " that&#146;s right.", "answer": " all right, chandler can make boxes, ross can wrap, and joey can lift things. now phoebe, go tell the guys they have to help out!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 57, "asentId": 58}, {"question": " okay.", "answer": " okay!  oh my god, thank you!!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 59, "asentId": 60}, {"question": "  okay! the movers will be here in 11 hours. rachel has not packed. now, everybody has to help! chandler, we&#146;re gonna start with&#133;", "answer": " oh nope, i-i have plans with joey.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 63, "asentId": 64}, {"question": " i thought you said you were going to do nothing.", "answer": " yes, but for the last time.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 65, "asentId": 66}, {"question": " okay fine, now ross&#133;", "answer": " oh, but-but i can&#146;t do it.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 67, "asentId": 68}, {"question": " why not?", "answer": "  i&#146;ve got ben.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 69, "asentId": 70}, {"question": " because, because i&#146;ve got ben.", "answer": " it&#146;s almost 8 o&#146;clock, it&#146;s almost past his bedtime. where-where is he?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 71, "asentId": 72}, {"question": " he&#146;s at a dinner party.", "answer": " is he really coming? because i can see right into your apartment!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 73, "asentId": 74}, {"question": " of course he is! what, do you think i&#146;d just use my son as-as an excuse? what kind of father do you think i am?", "answer": " all right, sorry.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 75, "asentId": 76}, {"question": " here it is! our last pizzas together as roommates.", "answer": " oh, i wish i&#146;d know you were going to do that, i ordered chinese.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 79, "asentId": 80}, {"question": " say, joe, i had a strange idea of what we could do for our last night. what do you say we play a little uh, foosball for money?", "answer": " what, are you crazy? you haven&#146;t beaten me once since my injury plagued &#146;97 season. it would be easier if you just give me your money.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 83, "asentId": 84}, {"question": " yes it would. what do you say to $50?", "answer": " okay, you&#146;re on.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 85, "asentId": 86}, {"question": " ohhhhhh, look it&#146;s the roller blades.", "answer": "  oh god!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 89, "asentId": 90}, {"question": " you remember when we got these?", "answer": " no.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 91, "asentId": 92}, {"question": " you guys, we said we were gonna have fun! come on, hey, remember the time&#133;  you don&#146;t remember?", "answer": " i&#146;m sorry pheebs, i guess i&#146;m just really said that i&#146;m leaving.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 95, "asentId": 96}, {"question": " i&#146;m gonna miss you so much.", "answer": " well, this doesn&#146;t have to be so sad though. y&#146;know? maybe instead of just thinking about how much you&#146;re gonna miss each other, you should like think of the things you&#146;re not gonna miss.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 97, "asentId": 98}, {"question": " i don&#146;t think there&#146;s anything.", "answer": " come on, there&#146;s gotta be something.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 99, "asentId": 100}, {"question": " nope, she&#146;s perfect.", "answer": " i have one.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 101, "asentId": 102}, {"question": " good! great! you can go first.", "answer": " uh well, i guess i&#146;m not gonna miss the fact that you&#146;re never allowed to move the phone pen.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 103, "asentId": 104}, {"question": " good that&#146;s a good one. okay, monica, anything? y&#146;know? does rachel move the phone pen?", "answer": " aw, sometimes. always, actually.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 105, "asentId": 106}, {"question": " okay, good. there you go. doesn&#146;t anyone feel better?", "answer": " not just the phone pen. i never get my messages.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 107, "asentId": 108}, {"question": " you get your messages!", "answer": " yeah, well i don&#146;t think it really counts if you have to read them off the back of your hand after you fall asleep on the couch.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 109, "asentId": 110}, {"question": " so-so, you missed a message from who? chandler or your mom? or chandler? or your mom?", "answer": " great! it worked! no one&#146;s sad.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 111, "asentId": 112}, {"question": "  yes! i win again! ha-ha! that&#146;s like 500 bucks you owe me! whoo-ho-hoo!  $500 that is a loooot of electricity!  whoo-ho-ho!  i gotta buy some food.", "answer": " okay, give me a chance to win my money back. okay? sudden death, one goal, $1,000.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 113, "asentId": 114}, {"question": " you serious?", "answer": " oh yes!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 115, "asentId": 116}, {"question": " okay, get ready to owe me!", "answer": " okay.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 117, "asentId": 118}, {"question": " hello?  oh, hi ross!  see? other people call me!", "answer": " ooh, your brother. score!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 125, "asentId": 126}, {"question": "  what&#146;s up?", "answer": " oh, i&#146;m just over here with ben. i thought we&#146;d say hi.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 127, "asentId": 128}, {"question": " oh, put him on!", "answer": " ben, say hi to aunt monica.  oh, i guess he doesn&#146;t feel like talking right now. he&#146;s smiling though! okay, talk to you later.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 129, "asentId": 130}, {"question": " yeah, i think it was better when you guys were sad. hey, uh, remember the roller blades?", "answer": " you know what else i&#146;m not gonna miss? &quot;i&#146;m monica. i wash the toilet 17 times a day. even if people are on it!&quot;", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 131, "asentId": 132}, {"question": " &quot;hi i&#146;m rachel, is my sweater too tight? no? oh, i&#146;d better wash it and shrink it!&quot;", "answer": " &quot;i&#146;m monica, i don&#146;t get phone messages from interesting people. ever!&quot;", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 133, "asentId": 134}, {"question": " hey! i call her!", "answer": " &quot;oh my god, i love ross! i hate ross! i love ross! i hate ross!&quot;", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 135, "asentId": 136}, {"question": " still broken?", "answer": " this sucks man! the last night you&#146;re here and i lose the two most important things in my life, the foosball table and $500.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 141, "asentId": 142}, {"question": " nah, not my game.", "answer": " okay, uh, how about, how about&#151;y&#146;know what? we could play a new game. a new game, it&#146;s fun.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 145, "asentId": 146}, {"question": " well, what&#146;s it called?", "answer": " cups.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 147, "asentId": 148}, {"question": " i don&#146;t know how to play cups.", "answer": " i&#146;ll teach ya! come on, come on, it&#146;s really easy and really, really fun.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 149, "asentId": 150}, {"question": " all right.", "answer": " okay, here you go.  i have two queens, what do you have?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 151, "asentId": 152}, {"question": " a two and a five.", "answer": " ho-ho, you win! 50 dollars!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 153, "asentId": 154}, {"question": " really?!", "answer": " oh yeah! okay, let&#146;s play again.  what do you got?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 155, "asentId": 156}, {"question": " a four and a nine.", "answer": " you&#146;re kidding right?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 157, "asentId": 158}, {"question": " no. why?", "answer": " well that&#146;s a full cup!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 159, "asentId": 160}, {"question": " i&#146;m not talking to her!", "answer": " well, one of you has to take the first step! and it should be you, because she&#146;s the one who&#146;s leaving. it&#146;s harder for her!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 163, "asentId": 164}, {"question": " well, maybe you&#146;re right&#151;she made fun of my phone pen!", "answer": " i know, i took it hard too.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 165, "asentId": 166}, {"question": " i&#146;m unpacking!", "answer": " what?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 169, "asentId": 170}, {"question": " i&#146;m not moving!  is that picture straight?", "answer": " it needs to go about 20 blocks to the left!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 171, "asentId": 172}, {"question": " hey, y&#146;know what? you&#146;re the one who wants to make this big change and move in with chandler! you should be the one to go! why should i have to leave?!", "answer": " because it&#146;s my apartment!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 173, "asentId": 174}, {"question": " well it&#146;s mine too! what else you got?!", "answer": " how about, you&#146;re moving!!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 175, "asentId": 176}, {"question": " hey, how are you guys doing?", "answer": " great! monica&#146;s moving!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 179, "asentId": 180}, {"question": "  i am not!", "answer": " oh really?! then how come all your stuff is in this box?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 181, "asentId": 182}, {"question": " okay, you guys. you guys i think i know what&#146;s going on here. okay, you guys&#133; stop!!  i know that, i know that you&#146;re acting mad because you think that it&#146;ll make it easier to leave. but deep down you&#146;re still really sad. deep-deep down.", "answer": " no phoebe i am mad!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 183, "asentId": 184}, {"question": " well, deep-deep-deep down!", "answer": " yeah, i&#146;m just mad!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 185, "asentId": 186}, {"question": " you win.", "answer": " well, what did you have?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 189, "asentId": 190}, {"question": " it doesn&#146;t matter because nothing beats a three and a six. that my friend is d-cup. okay, now much have you won so far?", "answer": " uh,  wow, 700.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 191, "asentId": 192}, {"question": " not 700 exactly?", "answer": " yeah.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 193, "asentId": 194}, {"question": " what?", "answer": " well you see in cups, once you get $700, you have to double it.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 197, "asentId": 198}, {"question": " really?", "answer": " hey, i didn&#146;t make up the rules. now, after you receive the doubling bonus, you get uh, one card. now that one card could be worth $100 bringing your total to 1,500.  don&#146;t get to excited because that&#146;s not gonna happen unless you get&#151;no way!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 199, "asentId": 200}, {"question": " well, this is the last box of your clothes. i&#146;m just gonna label it, &quot;what were you thinking?&quot;", "answer": " funny, because i was just gonna go across the hall and write that on chandler.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 201, "asentId": 202}, {"question": " hey you guys, i don&#146;t mean to make things worse, but umm, i don&#146;t want to live with rachel anymore. monica and rachel: what?!", "answer": " you&#146;re just so mean to each other! and i don&#146;t want to end up like that with rachel. i still like you!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 203, "asentId": 204}, {"question": " well, phoebe that&#146;s fine because i&#146;m not moving.", "answer": " whoa-whoa-whoa, phoebe you gotta take her! y&#146;know i-i-i said some really bad stuff about her, but y&#146;know rachel has some good qualities that make her a good roommate.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 205, "asentId": 206}, {"question": " oh really? like what monica?", "answer": " y&#146;know she has 147,000 pairs of boots&#133;", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 207, "asentId": 208}, {"question": " oh yeah, good start mon.", "answer": " she lets you borrow them.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 209, "asentId": 210}, {"question": " yeah and you stretch &#145;em out with your big old clown feet.", "answer": " do you wanna live outside?! because it&#146;s gettin&#146; cold!  she gets tons of catalogs and umm, she&#146;ll fold down the pages of the things she thinks that i&#146;d like.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 211, "asentId": 212}, {"question": " what else?", "answer": " when i take a shower, she leaves me little notes on the mirror.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 213, "asentId": 214}, {"question": " yeah, i do. i-i do, do that.", "answer": " that&#146;s nice. i like having things to read in the bathroom.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 215, "asentId": 216}, {"question": " when i fall asleep on the couch after reading, she covers me over with a blanket.", "answer": " well y&#146;know, i don&#146;t want you to be cold.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 217, "asentId": 218}, {"question": " oh, it&#146;s gonna be fine.", "answer": " okay rachel, i can&#146;t wait to live with you! and you know what we should do? bring monica and then we could all live there together! we&#146;ll have so much fun!!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 221, "asentId": 222}, {"question": " but honey, i think she&#146;s moving in with chandler.", "answer": " oh that&#146;s right. you&#146;re still set on that?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 223, "asentId": 224}, {"question": " hey!", "answer": " what&#146;s wrong?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 229, "asentId": 230}, {"question": " ross and i were helping the girls pack, took a little break, i lost $1,500 to him in cups!", "answer": " wh-how did you lose at cups?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 231, "asentId": 232}, {"question": " the same way you lost. i started out with a king and a queen, bamn! ross gets a 2 and a 3. then i get a jack and a king, boom! ross gets a 4 and a 5! ross was getting the cup card, the d-cup, the sittin&#146; down bonus! meanwhile, i didn&#146;t even get half a cup! nothin&#146;!!", "answer": " oh man!!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 233, "asentId": 234}, {"question": " and he never played before either! y&#146;know what i think? i think beginner&#146;s luck, very important in cups.", "answer": " all right, let&#146;s play one more hand! one more!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 235, "asentId": 236}, {"question": " no, no, no more! i cannot lose another dime! i&#146;m serious this time! in-in fact, look, there&#146;s a&#151;i wanna give you something. and let me give it too you know before i pawn it for cups money.  now, i want you to have the big white dog as a kinda of a, y&#146;know, thank you for being such a great roommate.", "answer": " i can&#146;t take the big white dog! you love it!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 237, "asentId": 238}, {"question": " it&#146;s him, not it!", "answer": " no, but wait&#151;what if i bought it from you, y&#146;know? and your nice gesture would be giving it to me at a reasonable price, say  $1,500?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 239, "asentId": 240}, {"question": " wait a second, i see what you&#146;re trying to do here! you-you&#146;re trying to give me money again!", "answer": " when did i try to give you money?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 241, "asentId": 242}, {"question": " over there!  before, with the bills! you tried to give some charity, i said &quot;no,&quot; you dropped it. okay? then we had a nice last night together, we had some fun, we gambled, nobody tried to give anybody any money! now out of the blue, you start with the charity thing again!", "answer": " i&#146;m just trying to help you out! okay? i wanna make sure that you&#146;re okay.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 243, "asentId": 244}, {"question": " hey. call me when you get there. okay?", "answer": " okay.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 247, "asentId": 248}, {"question": " thanks.", "answer": " yeah.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 253, "asentId": 254}, {"question": " yeah.", "answer": " bye house!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 257, "asentId": 258}, {"question": " bye mon.", "answer": " bye.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 259, "asentId": 260}, {"question": "  hey.", "answer": " she really left.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 261, "asentId": 262}, {"question": " thank you.", "answer": " no problem roomie.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 265, "asentId": 266}, {"question": " can i ask you a question?", "answer": " sure!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 267, "asentId": 268}, {"question": " i invented the game of cups as a way to give joey money.", "answer": " and now you want that money back.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 271, "asentId": 272}, {"question": " exactly.", "answer": " chandler, what kind of an idiot do you take me for?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 273, "asentId": 274}, {"question": " it&#146;s not a real game! i made it up!", "answer": " i&#146;m sorry you lost your money, but i won it fair and square.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 275, "asentId": 276}, {"question": " at a fake game!!", "answer": " now, if you wanna try to make some of it back, i&#146;d be glad to play you for it. but i should warn you, i am very good at cups.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 277, "asentId": 278}, {"question": " okay! now i assume the saucer card came up when you played last.", "answer": " no.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 279, "asentId": 280}]